NGHIA MINH TRUNG NGUYEN

Full-Stack Web Developer

+84 934 945 803 \$\diamonguyenminhtrungnghia@gmail.com \$\diamong github.com/JuneNghia

OBJECTIVE

With over 2 years of experience in creating web applications that significantly support individuals and organizations, I am always eager to contribute to the community through the products I've developed. Driven by a passion for creativity and constant discovery, I aim to challenge myself in large companies to learn and develop my skills, from knowledge to professional ethics. My next goal is to become a senior full-stack developer capable of training and leading teams in large, complex projects with extensive frontend and backend requirements.

EDUCATION

Master of Information Technology (In progress)

07/2024 - Present

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HUTECH)

Bachelor of Information Technology

08/2019 - 12/2023

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HUTECH), CGPA: 3.66/4.0

SKILLS

Main Programming Languages

Javascript

Technologies Used

React - NextJS - NestJS - MySQL - PostgreSQL - Typescript

Languages Spoken

Vietnamese - English AWS EC2 - AWS S3 - Docker - NGINX

EXPERIENCE

Others

CVT Technology Co., Ltd.

01/2023 - Present

Full-Stack Developer

- Communicate with clients/managers about desired features to develop.
- Analyze features to be developed with team members.
- Design and build databases.
- Design user interfaces using React and NPM libraries.
- Write APIs and collaborate with testers for functional integration testing.
- Integrate API interactions on the user interface.

MIHO Trading Service Co., Ltd.

02/2022 - 01/2023

Wordpress Developer

- Built product advertising websites and portfolios using WordPress and extended plugins.
- Supported technology-related issues like printers, computers, hardware, and software troubleshooting.
- Advised customers on products.
- Developed and maintained the following websites:
 - Miho Living (https://miholiving.net/)
 - Vietnam Hotel Furniture (https://vietnamhotelfurniture.com/)

NOTABLE PROJECTS

1. Thanh Tam Store (Client Project)

04/2024

- Managed products, customers, orders, calculated total revenue, etc.
- Technologies used: ReactJS, NestJS, MySQL, MUI, TypeORM, TailwindCSS, etc.
- Product URL: https://cuahangthanhtam.com

2. BSC Strategic Management (Company Project - Team Size: 4)

12/2023

- Assisted businesses and organization owners in building development strategies following the Balanced Score Card model.
- Technologies used: ReactJS, NestJS, Typescript, MySQL, Sequelize, TypeORM, MUI, TailwindCSS, etc.

3. UniQuiz (Personal Project)

08/2023

- Supported students with a reliable online multiple-choice quiz simulation aligned with the curriculum. Achieved over 2000+ users in three months after launch.
- Technologies used: ReactJS, ExpressJS, PostgreSQL, MUI, etc.
- Product URL: https://uniquiz.online/

ACHIEVEMENTS

Finalist at Hutech IT Got Talent	12/2022
Third Prize in Hutech Startup Wings competition	04/2022

CERTIFICATIONS

Communication and Teamwork Skills	04/2023
International Standard English B1	12/2022